http://www.vetsystems.com/index.php/privacy-policy

Skip to Main Content
MenuHomeAbout usVetStationsVetStation WindowsVetStation MacVetStation TabletVetStation ProVetStation DesktopVetStation MobileVetStation Mobile ProVetStation IRISVetStation ComparisonDDS Cluster TechnologySpectrumSpectrum OverviewConfigurationsClient and Animal RecordsClinical NotesEquine and Large AnimalInvoicingPaymentsFinancialInsuranceReportingOutpatient Client ManagementInpatient Client ManagementInternal CommunicationsExternal CommunicationsStock ManagementPractice Health PlansLaboratory ManagementWorkflow ManagementClient Relations and MarketingVisionVision OverviewEmailSMS MessagesRemote Access and DesktopSecure NetworkingManaged InternetNetworked CamerasPractice IntranetFile StorageRota ManagerRota ManagerRota Manager OverviewRota Manager BenefitsRota Manager FeaturesPersonnel ManagerPersonnel Manager BenefitsPersonnel Manager FeaturesIRISIRIS BenefitsIRIS FeaturesIRIS ConfigurationsVIPERUltralinkServicesSupportTrainingData Centre ManagementInstallation and Data ConversionLAN and WAN ManagementManagement ConsultancyContact us
Data Protection and Privacy Policy
Data Protection and Privacy Policy
Policy Statement
We respect your privacy and will not sell or make available in any way your personal data except where you have specifically asked us to do so. Personal data is only collected where necessary to service your requests.
From time to time we may need to update this Privacy Policy and publish via our website. Please visit this website for the latest copy of this policy or write to us at the address below.
The nature of the services provided by AT Veterinary Systems means that we might obtain certain information about you. This statement sets out the principles governing our use and handling of your data. By registering to use the services you agree to this use.
The collection and processing of personal data through AT Veterinary Systems is done in accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation. AT Veterinary Systems collects personal data through its websites via submission forms and website cookies. It also receives personal data sent in via email, text messages, social media posts and messaging platforms (e.g. Twitter), telephone, VOIP phone calls (e.g. Skype) and facsimile submissions, Royal Mail and other couriers.
What type of data is collected?
When you use the contact form on the website, engage with us on social media, download or install any of our software, enquire about our products and services, contact us with any queries, enter prize draws or competitions, complete any surveys, interact with us at trade shows and exhibitions, purchase any of our products or in any other way use the services of AT Veterinary Systems and related companies you may provide certain personal data. This data may include:
your first names and title
your surname
your address and previous addresses
email addresses
job title
your telephone number(s)
VAT registration number
details of interactions with us
details of your product preferences and service choices
information gathered from the use of cookies on our website(s)
technical information regarding your browser and internet connection including your IP address
Applicants for employment, training, volunteering, work experience and student placements also provide detailed information about education and previous experience via the online forms, application forms and Curriculum Vitae. This is required for the assessment of the working capacity of the employee and assessment for training and education purposes.
We may supplement the information that you provide us with information we receive from third parties.
If AT Veterinary Systems is acting as a data processor for your business, we will have a data processing agreement in place. This will detail what personal data we process on your behalf, the purposes, retention period and other obligations under the GDPR.
What are the legal bases for processing my data?
In some circumstances, AT Veterinary Systems will need to process your data to fulfil contractual obligations. For example, if you enter into a software agreement with us, we will provide backup storage and verification services.
The processing of your personal data may also be done to pursue legitimate interests that you can reasonably expect. These legitimate interests include marketing purposes, web analytics, personalisation, updating contact details, enhancement of services, network security enhancement, understanding web interaction, promotional campaigns, advertising, customer communication and for the distribution of information from AT Veterinary Systems and related companies under AT Veterinary Systems Limited and Central Veterinary Services Limited. We may also use the data you provide us in response to surveys and to aggregate user profiles.
Personal data submitted for training, employment and work experience purposes might be processed as part of the process of entering into a contract of employment, training or volunteer agreement.
Personal data submitted for training, employment and work experience purposes may also be processed as a legitimate interest where the data collected does not form part of a contractual agreement.
What are the purposes for collecting my data?
Purposes for collecting personal data include postal and electronic marketing, product development, developing security and privacy enhancing technologies, providing interesting content, customer support, training, improving service offering, statistical purposes, demographic analysis, distributing information regarding AT Veterinary Systems’ products and services, providing feedback, responding to queries and pet reunification.
You may unsubscribe from any communications by writing to us at the address below or following the link on electronic communications.
Will any of my data be given to third parties?
AT Veterinary Systems Ltd only passes data to third parties in the following circumstances;
when obligated by law, for instance in case of a lawful request by law enforcement authorities;
where a third party is engaged to deliver a service on behalf of AT Veterinary Systems or a customer and where third parties have a data processing agreement in place with us. This includes Central Veterinary Services Limited and the National Veterinary Database.
when you instruct us to do so, or give us consent to pass on your data.
No data will be passed outside the EEA.
You have the right to object to us using your data at any time. Please see the contact details below to inform us how you would like your data to be handled.
How long will my data be kept?
AT Veterinary Systems will store your personal data for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was provided, and to meet contractual, legal, audit and other regulatory requirements.
Data that is no longer required will be deleted, although some data may be retained for archiving purposes in the public interest or statistical purposes.
If you wish for your personal data to be amended or removed please write to us at the address below.
Will my personal data be secure?
We value your privacy. AT Veterinary Systems has therefore taken organisational and technical measures to protect your data from theft, loss or any kind of use that is not in line with the purposes for which the data was collected.
We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal data, but cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose online.
You accept the inherent security implications of working online over the Internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless we have been negligent or in wilful default.
AT Veterinary Systems may link to other websites and we are not responsible for their data policies or procedures, or for their content.
What rights do I have over my personal data?
You have the right to request:
access to your personal data
correction of your personal data if incorrect, out of date or incomplete
that we stop processing your data
You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority (the Information Commissioner’s Office).
Where can I file a request to access, rectify or remove my data?
Please see the contact details below.
Contact details
If you wish to contact someone at AT Veterinary Systems regarding privacy and the collection of personal data, please write to:
Data Security Co-ordinator
AT Veterinary Systems
Elmtree Business Park
Elmswell
Bury St Edmunds
Suffolk IP30 9HR.
Or Email: datasecurity@vetsystems.com
Please note this policy is continually updated and users are advised to refer to these pages before every submission of data
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
